[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Robert De Niro won his first Academy Award for the portrayal of this former boxing champion.", "correct_answer": "Jake LaMotta", "incorrect_answers": ["James Braddock", "Marcel Cerdan", "Nino Benvenuti"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is a traditional Vietnamese clothing, worn primarily by women?", "correct_answer": "\u00c1o d\u00e0i", "incorrect_answers": ["Qipao", "Nhu", "Raglan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mangoes are high in prebiotic dietary fiber and vitamin C.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement is true about John Larroquette ?", "correct_answer": "He has been a member of the Democratic Party.", "incorrect_answers": ["He is an avid Chicago Bears fan.", "He has served in the U.S. National Guard.", "He has been  a  member of the National Rifle Association."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many Earth years does it take for Jupiter to complete one orbit around the Sun?", "correct_answer": "11.8 years", "incorrect_answers": ["10.5 years", "22.4 years", "5.5 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these states has the biggest area?", "correct_answer": "Hawaii", "incorrect_answers": ["Washington, D.C.", "Connecticut", "Delaware"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why would mermaids drown humans according to popular belief and different stories?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Because they forget humans cant breathe underwater", "In attempts to rescue them from drowning", "Out of spite"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is not true about the Indian Elephant?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["It has a smaller trunk than the African Elephant.", "Its abdomen is quite large compared to its skull, unlike African elephants.", "It has larger ears than the African Elephant."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What caused the death of Wayne McLaren and David McLean, famous for appearing in many Marlboro television and print advertisements?", "correct_answer": "Lung cancer", "incorrect_answers": ["Car crash", "Horse accident", "Fire caused by a cigarette"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is what most graffiti artists prefer to be called.", "correct_answer": "Writers", "incorrect_answers": ["Sprayers", "Artists", "Painters"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These are the least painful parts of the body to put a tattoo on.", "correct_answer": "Fleshy parts of the arms and legs", "incorrect_answers": ["The shoulders", "The ankles", "The belly and the calf"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Makawao is the capital of the State of Hawaii.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]